chelsio.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Chelsio Communications

**Chelsio respects your privacy.**  
Chelsio Communications respects your privacy and is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This is reflected in our treatment of the personal information that we may collect from your use of www.chelsio.com and your interactions with Chelsio off-line. Our primary aim in collecting user information is to improve your experience on our web-site and to serve you better.  
  
**How Chelsio collects your personal information**  
In an attempt to enhance the user experience Chelsio may collect your information using but not limited to the following methods:  

  * Your e-mails to us
  * Your resume submissions to us
  * Your online purchases with us

**How Chelsio uses your information**  
The personal information that Chelsio collects is to understand your interests better and help us deliver a more personalized experience. For example, Chelsio may use your information to:  

  * Provide service and support
  * Educate you about our latest available products, services and special offers
  * Provide you with Chelsio related news updates
  * Assist you in completing a transaction or order

For our services that require payment we collect your credit card information (such as account name, number and expiration date), which is used for our or our agent’s billing purposes only, and is not otherwise shared.  
  
**How Chelsio shares your information**  
In our commitment to protect your privacy Chelsio will not sell, rent, share or lease your personal information to others.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at [privacy@chelsio.com](mailto:privacy@chelsio.com)
